<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GitHub on Website of Jane Doe</title>
    <link>https://adamchen99.github.io/tags/github/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GitHub on Website of Jane Doe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adamchen99.github.io/tags/github/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 3</title>
      <link>https://adamchen99.github.io/post/project_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamchen99.github.io/post/project_3/</guid>
      <description>Link Click Here to access Github of the code.
Learning Objectives  Continue practice working with multiple input files Use relative filename paths instead of absolute filenames Implement a sorted tree such as a Binary Search Tree in Java Perform traversal operation on binary search tree If you choose Java, a review of Java concepts such as  Creating classes, and instantiating them Creating a node class to be re-used in a linked list class   If you choose another language, getting acquainted enough to work with tree data structure  Problem Description A local Radio DJ wants to create a sorted playlist based on the song title name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2</title>
      <link>https://adamchen99.github.io/post/project_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamchen99.github.io/post/project_2/</guid>
      <description>Link Click Here to access Github of the code.
Learning Objectives  Continue practice putting together a small project with input file and output file If you choose Java, a review of Java concepts  Creating classes, and instantiating them Creating a node class to be re-used in a linked list class   If you choose another language, getting acquainted enough to work with linked list data structure  Problem Description A record label executive received text files that contain the top streamed music artists during certain weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>https://adamchen99.github.io/post/project_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamchen99.github.io/post/project_1/</guid>
      <description>Link Click Here to access Github of the code.
Learning Objectives  Putting together a small project with input file and output file If you choose Java, a review of Java concepts  Java array type, and 2D arrays Creating classes, and instantiating them   If you choose another language, getting acquainted enough to produce the report  Problem Description A record label executive received text files that contain the top streamed music artists during certain weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
